if(Moves.find().count() !== 0) {
} else {
  var doubleUnderhooksId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Double underhooks pass',
    video_id: 'xDe2pUDlTx8',
    video_start: 3
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "How do you begin?",
    question_video_start: 3,
    question_video_end: 12,
    answer_video_end: 18
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "What do you do with your knees?",
    question_video_start: 13,
    question_video_end: 17,
    answer_video_end: 23,
    answer_text: "Keep one knee up at first and then put both to the ground"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "What's another way of entering?",
    question_video_start: 22,
    question_video_end: 25,
    answer_video_end: 40
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "How do you enter if they're sitting up?",
    question_video_start: 40,
    question_video_end: 43,
    answer_video_end: 52
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "What's one of the most important things with this pass?",
    question_video_start: 51,
    question_video_end: 57,
    answer_video_end: 61,
    answer_text: "Controlling their hips"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "What happens if you reach for the collar straight away?",
    question_video_start: 71,
    question_video_end: 76,
    answer_video_end: 85
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "What should you do instead to prevent that?",
    question_video_start: 76,
    question_video_end: 85,
    answer_video_end: 110
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "What's the first way of lifting?",
    question_video_start: 110,
    question_video_end: 113,
    answer_video_end: 118
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "What's his preferred way of lifting?",
    question_video_start: 113,
    question_video_end: 118,
    answer_video_end: 140
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_video_start: 118,
    question_video_end: 140,
    answer_video_end: 152
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_video_start: 152,
    question_video_end: 173,
    answer_video_end: 194
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_video_start: 173,
    question_video_end: 194,
    answer_video_end: 212
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "How does he like to reach?",
    question_video_start: 194,
    question_video_end: 212,
    answer_video_end: 221
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_video_start: 212,
    question_video_end: 221,
    answer_video_end: 233
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_video_start: 212,
    question_video_end: 220,
    answer_video_end: 245
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: doubleUnderhooksId,
    question_text: "What should your hands do now?",
    question_video_start: 220,
    question_video_end: 245,
    answer_video_end: 271
  });


  var guardRecoveryFromToreandoKneeOnBellyId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Guard recovery from toreando knee on belly',
    video_id: 'vImvnDFX1y8'
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: guardRecoveryFromToreandoKneeOnBellyId,
    question_text: "What do you do first?",
    question_video_start: 11,
    question_video_end: 14,
    answer_video_end: 19,
    answer_text: "Block the shoulder"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: guardRecoveryFromToreandoKneeOnBellyId,
    question_video_start: 14,
    question_video_end: 19,
    answer_video_end: 28,
    answer_text: "Hip away"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: guardRecoveryFromToreandoKneeOnBellyId,
    question_video_start: 19,
    question_video_end: 28,
    answer_video_end: 34,
    answer_text: "The top leg comes in and you lift your hips to recover"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: guardRecoveryFromToreandoKneeOnBellyId,
    question_text: "Where can the top foot go?",
    question_video_start: 43,
    question_video_end: 46,
    answer_video_end: 51,
    answer_text: "The shoulder or the hip"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: guardRecoveryFromToreandoKneeOnBellyId,
    question_text: "How do you begin dealing with the knee on belly?",
    question_video_start: 54,
    question_video_end: 60,
    answer_video_end: 62,
    answer_text: "Block their hips"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: guardRecoveryFromToreandoKneeOnBellyId,
    question_text: "What do you do after blocking their hips?",
    question_video_start: 60,
    question_video_end: 62,
    answer_video_end: 67
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: guardRecoveryFromToreandoKneeOnBellyId,
    question_text: "What does he not want to see?",
    question_video_start: 67,
    question_video_end: 69,
    answer_video_end: 82
  });

  var halfGuardToButterflyId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Half guard to butterfly guard',
    video_id: 'rg6clVjzT5U'
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToButterflyId,
    question_text: "When would you use this instead of the half guard to closed guard escape?",
    question_video_start: 0,
    question_video_end: 11,
    answer_video_end: 20,
    answer_text: "Their grip is so tight that you can't get your arms under their head"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToButterflyId,
    question_text: "How do you begin?",
    question_video_start: 11,
    question_video_end: 20,
    answer_video_end: 25,
    answer_text: "Your right foot traps the leg and the left foot goes on the mat"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToButterflyId,
    question_text: "What does your right hand do?",
    question_video_start: 20,
    question_video_end: 26,
    answer_video_end: 29,
    answer_text: "Block their hip"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToButterflyId,
    question_text: "How do you begin inserting the butterfly?",
    question_video_start: 26,
    question_video_end: 29,
    answer_video_end: 40,
    answer_text: "Hip escape, get onto your right side and get a hook"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToButterflyId,
    question_text: "What happens if you start lifting them from here?",
    question_video_start: 29,
    question_video_end: 40,
    answer_video_end: 46,
    answer_text: "They will pass"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToButterflyId,
    question_text: "How should you do instead?",
    question_video_start: 40,
    question_video_end: 46,
    answer_video_end: 54,
    answer_text: "Square your hips back up"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToButterflyId,
    question_text: "How do you lift them now?",
    question_video_start: 46,
    question_video_end: 54,
    answer_video_end: 71,
    answer_text: "Grab on the back with your left hand, right hand on their hip and bring your knees towards your head"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToButterflyId,
    question_text: "How do you get the last hook in?",
    question_video_start: 54,
    question_video_end: 71,
    answer_video_end: 77
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToButterflyId,
    question_text: "How do you finish?",
    question_video_start: 71,
    question_video_end: 77,
    answer_video_end: 81,
    answer_text: "Sit up and sweep"
  });


  var halfGuardToClosedId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Half guard to closed guard',
    video_id: 'dUIg06rIU4A'
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToClosedId,
    question_text: "What's the first thing you should do?",
    question_video_start: 20,
    question_video_end: 23,
    answer_video_end: 34,
    answer_text: "Alleviate the pressure by pulling their shoulder down"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToClosedId,
    question_text: "How do you insert the arm under their chin?",
    question_video_start: 23,
    question_video_end: 34,
    answer_video_end: 58,
    answer_text: "Use your outer leg to hip escape and insert the arm"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToClosedId,
    question_text: "What do you do after inserting the first arm?",
    question_video_start: 34,
    question_video_end: 58,
    answer_video_end: 62,
    answer_text: "Hip out again and bring both arms in"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToClosedId,
    question_text: "How do you continue from here?",
    question_video_start: 58,
    question_video_end: 62,
    answer_video_end: 76,
    answer_text: "Hip out again while trapping them with your bottom leg and insert the knee shield"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToClosedId,
    question_text: "How should your left arm be positioned?",
    question_video_start: 62,
    question_video_end: 76,
    answer_video_end: 84,
    answer_text: "Underneath the knee shield to support it"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToClosedId,
    question_text: "How do you set your grips now?",
    question_video_start: 76,
    question_video_end: 84,
    answer_video_end: 93,
    answer_text: "Left hand on the collar, right hand on their sleeve"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: halfGuardToClosedId,
    question_text: "How do you get to the closed guard from here?",
    question_video_start: 84,
    question_video_end: 93,
    answer_video_end: 106,
    answer_text: "Maintain space, right foot on their hip, lift your hips and square up and close the guard"
  });


  var hqToNearSideKneeThroughId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Headquarters to near side knee through',
    video_id: 'XYZRqqY9Baw'
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_video_start: 12,
    question_video_end: 23,
    answer_video_end: 32
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_text: "Where does your left hand grab?",
    question_video_start: 23,
    question_video_end: 33,
    answer_video_end: 34
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_text: "Why?",
    question_video_start: 33,
    question_video_end: 34,
    answer_video_end: 49
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_text: "What can they do if you don't keep your elbow low?",
    question_video_start: 34,
    question_video_end: 49,
    answer_video_end: 57
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_video_start: 49,
    question_video_end: 57,
    answer_video_end: 67
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_video_start: 57,
    question_video_end: 67,
    answer_video_end: 79
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_text: "How should you place your left leg?",
    question_video_start: 57,
    question_video_end: 79,
    answer_video_end: 87
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_video_start: 79,
    question_video_end: 87,
    answer_video_end: 112
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_text: "What 2 ways can you finish?",
    question_video_start: 87,
    question_video_end: 112,
    answer_video_end: 147
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: hqToNearSideKneeThroughId,
    question_text: "What's an important detail about your right leg?",
    question_video_start: 112,
    question_video_end: 147,
    answer_video_end: 193
  });

  var headquartersToXPassId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Headquarters to x pass',
    video_id: 'lqFNFSIpC9Q'
  });

  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: headquartersToXPassId,
    question_text: "When would you go for this pass?",
    question_video_start: 3,
    question_video_end: 8,
    answer_video_end: 16,
    answer_text: "When she's not grabbing your leg"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: headquartersToXPassId,
    question_text: "Where do you grab?",
    question_video_start: 13,
    question_video_end: 16,
    answer_video_end: 23,
    answer_text: "The lapel and the outside of the leg"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: headquartersToXPassId,
    question_text: "What do you do once you've got your grips?",
    question_video_start: 16,
    question_video_end: 23,
    answer_video_end: 31
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: headquartersToXPassId,
    question_text: "What's the next step?",
    question_video_start: 23,
    question_video_end: 31,
    answer_video_end: 36
  });

  var kneeThroughFromHQId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Knee through pass from headquarters',
    video_id: 'jaIKWl1jgxU'
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "What is headquarters?",
    question_video_start: 3,
    question_video_end: 11,
    answer_video_end: 50,
    answer_text: "You've got one leg trapped and you're holding the lapel"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "How do you set your grips?",
    question_video_start: 11,
    question_video_end: 50,
    answer_video_end: 58,
    answer_text: "Hold the collar and the outside of the knee"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "Why is it important to hold the outside first?",
    question_video_start: 50,
    question_video_end: 58,
    answer_video_end: 75,
    answer_text: "They can recover guard"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "How should you position your body?",
    question_video_start: 58,
    question_video_end: 75,
    answer_video_end: 100,
    answer_text: "Pulling backwards and keeping your elbow tight"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "How do you begin the pass?",
    question_video_start: 75,
    question_video_end: 100,
    answer_video_end: 111,
    answer_text: "Shift the grip to the inside of the knee and the right hand goes to their hip"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "How do you get the knee across?",
    question_video_start: 100,
    question_video_end: 111,
    answer_video_end: 132,
    answer_text: "Move your body across and drop the knee next to their hip"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "Why should the left leg be positioned like this?",
    question_video_start: 111,
    question_video_end: 132,
    answer_video_end: 138,
    answer_text: "If it's too close to their arms, they can sweep you"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "What do you do after putting the knee down?",
    question_video_start: 131,
    question_video_end: 138,
    answer_video_end: 153,
    answer_text: "Crossface by grabbing under their armpit and pull in"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "What happens if you try to slide the knee straight away?",
    question_video_start: 138,
    question_video_end: 153,
    answer_video_end: 177,
    answer_text: "They'll hip escape and recover their guard. You need to have upper body control first."
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "How do you finish the pass?",
    question_video_start: 153,
    question_video_end: 177,
    answer_video_end: 191,
    answer_text: "Put forward pressure on the upper body and put the knee down"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: kneeThroughFromHQId,
    question_text: "Why shouldn't you think of this as a slide away?",
    question_video_start: 153,
    question_video_end: 191,
    answer_video_end: 220,
    answer_text: "You don't control their hips as well"
  });

  var makingPostureId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Making posture and dealing with grips in closed guard',
    video_id: '3iBSThL6BVw'
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: makingPostureId,
    question_text: "How do you deal with a collar grip if you have posture?",
    question_video_start: 20,
    question_video_end: 26,
    answer_video_end: 39,
    answer_text: "Use both hands to break the grip while you posture up, then keep holding their sleeve"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: makingPostureId,
    question_text: "How do you deal with a collar grip if it is deep and you can't break the grip, but their arm is still straight?",
    question_video_start: 26,
    question_video_end: 39,
    answer_video_end: 80,
    answer_text: "Lock their arm and put your elbow on their hip. Roll the head under the arm and then you can choose to break the grip."
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: makingPostureId,
    question_text: "What's the one thing you shouldn't do when your posture is broken down?",
    question_video_start: 38,
    question_video_end: 80,
    answer_video_end: 90,
    answer_text: "Turn the other way to expose your neck for a choke"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: makingPostureId,
    question_text: "How do you deal with the collar grip when your posture is broken down?",
    question_video_start: 80,
    question_video_end: 90,
    answer_video_end: 129,
    answer_text: "Keep the head down until you can block the opposite arm. Reach for the collar and stand up and make them release your collar by applying pressure."
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: makingPostureId,
    question_text: "What if they have your head?",
    question_video_start: 90,
    question_video_end: 129,
    answer_video_end: 142,
    answer_text: "Put both hands in and posture up"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: makingPostureId,
    question_text: "What if they have an overhook?",
    question_video_start: 129,
    question_video_end: 142,
    answer_video_end: 183,
    answer_text: "Put your head underneath their shin, stand up and pressure forward. Block their hips with your legs and pull the arm out quickly"
  });


  var recoveryFromOverUnderId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Recovery from over under',
    video_id: 'h8zt0LrKnW4'
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: recoveryFromOverUnderId,
    question_text: "How do you begin?",
    question_video_start: 4,
    question_video_end: 29,
    answer_video_end: 42,
    answer_text: "As soon as you feel them lifting the leg and going for the collar, lift your hips to keep the head to head distance"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: recoveryFromOverUnderId,
    question_text: "What do you do next?",
    question_video_start: 29,
    question_video_end: 42,
    answer_video_end: 67,
    answer_text: "Turn onto your side and move your hips away to recover the guard"
  });


// Moves.insert({
//   title: 'Submissions from closed guard',
//   video_id: '/videos/Submissions from closed guard.mp4'
// });

  var toreandoToKneeOnBellyId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Toreando pass to knee on belly',
    video_id: 'XP1m1ONaVJI'
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: toreandoToKneeOnBellyId,
    question_text: "How do you begin the pass?",
    question_video_start: 5,
    question_video_end: 7,
    answer_video_end: 12
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: toreandoToKneeOnBellyId,
    question_text: "What do you do when you get blocked?",
    question_video_start: 7,
    question_video_end: 13,
    answer_video_end: 21
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: toreandoToKneeOnBellyId,
    question_text: "What do you do once you have the knee on belly?",
    question_video_start: 16,
    question_video_end: 21,
    answer_video_end: 26,
    answer_text: "Stabilise and keep the other leg out so she can't grab it"
  });

  var toreandoWithShoulderPressureId = Moves.insert({
    title: 'Toreando pass with shoulder pressure',
    video_id: 'QjjDWIp_rOg'
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: toreandoWithShoulderPressureId,
    question_text: "How do you set your grips?",
    question_video_start: 2,
    question_video_end: 7,
    answer_video_end: 13,
    answer_text: "One hand on the inside of the knee, the other one on the hip"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: toreandoWithShoulderPressureId,
    question_text: "How do you begin the pass?",
    question_video_start: 7,
    question_video_end: 13,
    answer_video_end: 19,
    answer_text: "Walk to the side"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: toreandoWithShoulderPressureId,
    question_text: "What's an important detail about the their far leg?",
    question_video_start: 13,
    question_video_end: 19,
    answer_video_end: 43,
    answer_text: "You have to track it with your right arm and keep the head close, otherwise they may get the leg in and you won't pass"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: toreandoWithShoulderPressureId,
    question_text: "How do you continue the pass?",
    question_video_start: 19,
    question_video_end: 43,
    answer_video_end: 73,
    answer_text: "Push the knee down, get your shoulder into their stomach and walk into their legs"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: toreandoWithShoulderPressureId,
    question_text: "Why do you walk into their legs?",
    question_video_start: 43,
    question_video_end: 73,
    answer_video_end: 75,
    answer_text: "To kill their hips"
  });
  FlashCards.insert({
    moveId: toreandoWithShoulderPressureId,
    question_text: "How do you finish the pass?",
    question_video_start: 73,
    question_video_end: 75,
    answer_video_end: 86,
    answer_text: "Head goes down, underhook and walk back to flatten them out"
  });
}